callferret.com 2011-09-11

# CallFerret.com Privacy Policy

CallFerret needs your help ! Please take a quick look at our [donation support page](http://www.gofundme.com/callferret "Support CallFerret") and keep information free and highly visible...

Please read the terms and conditions of use before using this site: <http://www.callferret.com/terms.html>. By continuing to access or use this site, or any service on this site, you signify YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE.

CallFerret.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website:

_Note: This privacy policy also refers to account registration, forums and other features that are not yet enabled on the site._

By accepting this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use , you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to our terms of use.

This Privacy Policy contains a number of references to other information pages on our Site and other websites. Please note: underlined words and phrases are click-through links to these pages and websites. We strongly recommend that as you read this Privacy Policy, and you click on such links to obtain further important details about the Privacy Policy, as they may contain further terms and conditions which apply to you.

We will never sell or rent your personal information to third parties except as described in this Privacy Policy. If you object to your information being transferred or used in this way please do not register or provide us with such information. If you have any questions, send an email to [tosprivacy@callferret.com](mailto:tosprivacy@callferret.com).

## Overview

Your Privacy is very important to us. As part of the normal operation of our services we collect and, in some cases, may disclose information about you. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information. As described below, some of your personally identifiable information is disclosed to third parties and used by us and third parties. By accepting the Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information.

## Information Collection, Use, Sharing and Disclosure

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website and services. Through customer surveys, subscriptions, and newsletter registrations, our site may request users to give us contact, demographic and/or financial information (such as their name, locale, gender, age, income level and email address). The demographic information is used, among other things, to enhance user experience so we can be more content specific. The contact information is used to notify users of new services and content, as well as for surveys and newsletters. Contact information is also used to get in touch with the subscribers when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future communications; see the choice/opt-out section below. This site contains links to other sites. CallFerret.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites or any website from which you may have linked to CallFerret.com.

CallFerret.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. Please read this privacy policy to fully understand how we will make use of the personal information you share with us. CallFerret.com collects certain personal information in order to provide you with customized services, content, and advertisements. Some personal information is gathered when you register to receive certain CallFerret.com products or services. We may disclose to third parties certain aggregate information contained in your registration data or related data, provided that, such information will NOT include personally identifying information, except as specifically authorized by you or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with the law, legal process, or to enforce the terms of service. CallFerret.com will also use your personal information for the purposes of providing you with any services to which you subscribe, and any service-related activities such as collecting subscription fees from you for those services, and notifying you or contacting you regarding any problem with, or the expiration of, such services. In this regard, it may be necessary for CallFerret.com to disclose your personal information to one or more agents and contractors of CallFerret.com and their subcontractors, but such agents, contractors, and subcontractors will be required to agree to use the information obtained from CallFerret.com only for these purposes. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. CallFerret.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to sign out of your CallFerret.com account and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, CallFerret.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. CallFerret.com reserves the right to change this statement at any time by posting revisions on the CallFerret.com web site. This privacy policy is not intended to, and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of us.

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our Site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private.

## Children

CallFerret.com products and services are directed at an adult market, and therefore this site is intended for use by adults only. CallFerret.com encourages parents to take an active role in their children's use of the Internet, and to inform them of the dangers of providing information about themselves over the Internet. Children of any age should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. No information should be submitted to or posted on this web site by users under 18 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. Children are not eligible to use our services and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with your parents or guardians.

## Advertisements

Ads appearing on this web site are delivered to you by either (a) one of our web advertising partners or (b) by us. Information about your visit to this site, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad, your browser type (for example, Firefox or Internet Explorer), the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for instance) and whether or not you responded to the ad delivered, (but not your name, address, phone number or other personal information), is used to serve advertisements to you on this site. We may use your zip code or geographical location information to serve advertisements to this site. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie(s) on your browser. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. We aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. Certain information, such as your name, email address, password are never disclosed to marketing advertisers. This site may use its own proprietary ad serving system. However, this site may use and allow for third party ad serving systems (i.e.: Commission Junction, Google Adsense, Double-click, Mediaplex, ValueClick, etc.). Third party ad serving systems are approved at the site's discretion. The site and its third party servers collect and store anonymous data, typically through the use of cookies.

## Public Forums

This site contains comments, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. We request users to give us contact information, such as name, email, address, occupation, and interests to be a registered bulletin board user. This information is optional and not necessary to post messages. This information may be used by the administrator to send the user email notices. However, users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and users should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information publicly on the Internet.

## Security

While CallFerret.com cannot guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur, we do take great care to insure that your private information is as safe as possible through the use of secure technology and internal processes. As an example, any information that we collect about you is stored in an access-controlled environment, preventing access by unauthorized people. Your account is also password protected, and allows you to modify or update your information at any time.

## Choice/Opt-Out – Your ability to opt-out and remove your information.

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service: 

  * Users can send email to [tosprivacy@callferret.com](mailto:tosprivacy@callferret.com)
  * Users can call the following telephone number: 1-775-878-6240

## Contacting the Website 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact:

CallFerret.com  
1-775-878-6240
